Is this your Rolls Royce?
Yeah.
I have the biggest business media channel in
the entire world called the School of Hard
Knocks where I interview guys like Shaq, Mark Cuban.
What did you do to get a Rolls Royce?
I invented .
This car was 520 grand.
I could buy 100 of them brand new.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
How old were you when you made your first million?
About 34.
What do you do for a
living out here in Beverly Hills?
I actually roll burritos for a living.
You roll burritos?
I do.
What do you mean?
I'm the CEO of Chipotle Mexican Grill.
You're the CEO of Chipotle?
I am.
What's the most amount of money you
made in a single year as a CEO?
Nine million.
Nine million dollars?
What was the worst financial decision
that you made throughout your career?
Marriage.
Actually?
No, marrying the wrong person.
Excuse me, sir.
How did you get rich?
Excuse me?
Who said I was rich?
Come on, I can tell.
Come on.
I'm just a boy.
Just like all y'all.
What did you do to become wealthy?
What line of business were you in?
You're not with the news, are you?
No.
I was part of an organized crime group in
New York and I made my first million dollars
that way.
Organized crime?
Organized crime.
Mafia.
That's the last message to the younger generation.
Give them one more that's not,
because you were a high school dropout.
I was.
But you made more than
99.9% of business professors ever were.
That's fair.
Give them one more tactical lesson
about business that's not taught in school.
I always say two things too.
You want success in life?
Get these two things right.
Number one.
Guys, today I'm in Beverly Hills, one of
the wealthiest zip codes in the entire world,
home to some of the richest people on planet Earth.
And today I'm going to be
cold approaching multi-millionaires and billionaires out here
in Beverly Hills to ask them the real question.
That everybody wants to know.
How did you get rich and build your fortune?
We're going to be figuring out what
these people did to build multi-million dollar and
billion dollar companies and how you can do the same.
So stay tuned until the end
because this one's going to be crazy.
But let's get this video on the way.
Is this your Rolls Royce?
Yeah.
I have the biggest business media channel in
the entire world called the School of Hard Knocks.
Where I interview guys like Shaq, Mark Cuban.
What did you do?
What did you do to get a Rolls Royce?
I invented gel nails, 1981.
Actually, have you always been a business owner?
1981, I invented gel.
What's the greatest lesson you've
learned about entrepreneurship since 1981?
That's 40 years ago.
40 years of business.
44 years ago.
You got to keep trying, motherfucker.
What's the most amount of money
you made in a single year?
I made over a hundred million.
How did you scale out to
do over nine figures in sales?
What was your secret to scaling?
I started with $200 on Venice Beach.
Here's a picture of the first day on Venice Beach.
Oh my gosh.
And you invented that.
How were you an engineer?
I was an engineer.
You were an engineer?
Yeah.
I was an engineer.
How important was it for you kind of
being an innovator and thinking like, how did you
come up with that idea?
Tell me.
I used gel on my teeth.
I took it from my teeth.
It stays in your teeth or stay on your hands.
Were you a good salesman?
I always sell.
Sell every day.
What's your secret to selling?
You got to sell yourself first.
I got to go.
There you go.
Can we pull up here
real quick for one more minute?
It'll be worth it.
I promise you.
We do 200 million views a month.
200 million?
Yes, sir.
And we have 12.7 million across social media followers.
So it'll be worth it.
Just take a look.
I'm going to take a look.
You want to take a look at TikTok?
Yes, sir.
I got a chance to
buy part of TikTok next week.
Are you serious?
Are you thinking about it?
It's a lot of money, but
it's the best platform in the world.
Absolutely.
Did you borrow any money at any point in time?
Did you raise money or was it all bootstrapped?
Never had a line of credit.
Never had a mortgage.
Never borrowed money in 44 years.
Actually, why not?
You didn't want to take on that risk?
All from profit.
Sell gel for $25.
That cost a dollar.
How'd you scale?
Just kept putting the profit back in.
Just reinvest and reinvest.
What's more important, product or distribution?
Product and distribution.
I'm in 90 countries.
If you don't have the product, can't supply.
How'd you go global?
Because a lot of people, they don't
think about those international markets that they
can get into.
1980s, I started traveling all over the world myself.
Africa, 26 hours with a half hour stopover.
I knew in the 80s that global was the play.
What were those conversations
like getting into foreign markets?
Because a lot of people, they
hear people say, oh, globalization, globalization.
How do you actually go in-
Follow you on YouTube.
Thanks, brother.
I appreciate it.
I'm not him, but I still follow you.
I appreciate you.
It means a lot.
You don't get to go
in until you find somebody good.
Were you a good negotiator?
My mother said I could sell
a cat off a dead fish truck.
Did you come from a rich family?
No, my father was a plumber.
He used to clean shit in toilets.
Now, as a $100 million entrepreneur, what's
the best financial advice you've been given?
The best financial advice in the world?
Save your fucking money and
don't waste it on stupid shit.
This car was 520 grand.
I bought it at an auction for 175.
I could buy 100 of them brand new,
but I wouldn't spend 500,000 on a car.
Do you believe in God?
Of course I believe in God.
I wouldn't be here if it wasn't.
How important has faith been for your success?
Did you always-
Did you always have that belief in God, or
was it something that you got at a later age
when you realized how important it was?
I think the most important religion in the world
is act on to others you wish them to
act on to you.
Don't do anything to anybody you wouldn't want
them to do to you or your daughter.
Now, you're sitting in a Rolls Royce.
This is a lot of people's dream car.
How can somebody own a Rolls Royce in today's world?
Give me one more golden nugget that
a lot of people are missing out on.
The younger generation, what are they missing out
on in terms of business and creating financial
freedom and creating the life that they want to live?
The best thing to do is keep trying.
Babe Ruth led the league in home
runs and strikeouts in the same year.
This wasn't my first business.
I failed three times before.
I was 18, 19, and 22, but I
kept shooting, and then I hit the big one.
So you got to just keep trying.
You can't give up.
Could I get your number?
Yeah, sure.
Absolutely.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate that.
It means a lot to me.
Thank you, sir.
You asked good questions.
That's why you got a big following.
Yes, sir.
It's different.
You kept good questions coming.
Absolutely.
I have a friend who's an entrepreneur
who was pulling up in his Rolls Royce.
You know I had to stop him for that
interview, but my favorite part about that entire interview
was when he said, save your money.
Listen, the wealthiest people that I know
are some of the most frugal people.
He said, I could buy 500 of these Rolls
Royces brand new and in cash, but he chooses not
to because he's focused on building an empire.
Crazy start to this Beverly Hills video.
We got to keep this one rolling and
go get another one out here, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
How did you get rich?
Excuse me?
Who said I was rich?
Come on.
I can tell.
I'm just a boy.
Just like all y'all.
What business were you in?
I'm in the oil and gas business.
I drill oil wells in Kansas.
That's what I do.
How did you get into oil and gas?
Did you come from a lot of money?
I did not.
I came from nothing.
I'm a high school dropout, brother.
So what was your turning point to financial freedom?
If it wasn't instilled in you-
Financial freedom.
I think everybody's trying to get there, bro.
You, me, her.
So you're drilling oil and gas.
Are you kind of doing the model where
you're going to people's houses where you find the
oil and you're like-
No, I'm not the land man.
I'm just the guy who puts the deals together.
So you're the middleman.
Something like that.
There's a saying that I heard one
time, I interviewed a really successful Wall Street
gentleman that whenever wealth is transferred
from one person to another, there's somebody
in the middle there transferring the wealth.
That person also becomes wealthy.
Is that kind of what you're
saying is what's going on here?
I think you could look at it that way.
Right.
Give me your best sales and negotiation advice right here.
That's one of the biggest components that I've seen-
Don't take no for an answer.
So you're big on persistence.
How many times did you try to get a yes?
Like put it in perspective for them.
How hard it was to get those yeses sometimes.
Some transactions come together
easier than others, my friend.
Did you own a business?
I own many businesses.
Are you diversified?
Or is it just oil and gas?
I'm involved in a couple of different things.
I don't have any more time
to give you though, my friend.
Could we get a minute with you walking real quick?
Is that okay?
Sure.
Why not?
What do you want to talk about?
What else do you want to talk about?
All right.
So across these businesses, in terms of total
revenue, what was the most amount of money
you made in a year?
Yeah, that's kind of a personal question.
Just revenue.
I don't feel really comfortable answering the question.
Would you say more than $10 million?
Could be.
More than 100?
No, certainly not.
Definitely more than 10 million.
If it was 100 million, I would be off
in the south of France hanging out right now.
I'm not talking to three of you.
We're definitely in Beverly Hills though.
We are.
So let me ask you this.
How did you scale from a
seven figure to an eight figure business?
Let's talk about scaling.
Listen, I'm a one man operation.
You just got to be ready
for the opportunity when it finds you.
Do you think that you could have scaled
a lot more if you brought other people in?
Sure.
If I didn't spend so much time doing
other things and enjoying life, I probably could
have.
Now give me the best financial advice
that you ever got from a mentor.
Don't be afraid to spend money.
You'll always make more.
Scare money, don't make money is what you're saying.
I mean, that's us saying, but that's a different thing.
What I'm saying is when you're out there hustling.
Trying to make it happen.
Don't be afraid to spend a few
dollars and enjoy yourself along the way.
So was there an investment that you made where
a lot of people were kind of telling you not
to do it or they were doubting you maybe
in an instance and if so, kind of what happened?
I think that's a good question, but I
don't have an answer for that question other than
to tell you I'm going that way.
It's been real.
Yeah.
Enjoy your afternoon.
Your last message to the younger generation.
Give them one more.
That's not because you were a high school
dropout, but you, but you made more than 99.9%
of business professors ever.
Give them one more tactical lesson about business.
It's not taught in school.
Don't take the first no or the second no.
You got to be able to.
To keep pushing forward.
Last one because you're an oil
and gas is such a niche business.
How does that, how does that even happen?
How do you even get into it?
You know, I met someone on the
internet and we went into business together.
He was already in the business.
So relationships are very important.
They are.
You think what you know or
who you know is more important.
I think it depends on
what you do for a living.
I think in some cases who you
know is more important than what you know.
And in other cases, what you know is everything.
But when you first started,
you were a high school dropout.
And this guy doesn't take
no for a fucking answer here.
You're going to have to edit this part out.
But real quick, you're a high school dropout.
You didn't have credibility.
How did you build that first relationship?
With a successful person to
take you places that money can't.
I run people over for fun, my friend.
What do you do?
That means if you want something badly enough, you
got to go out there and make it happen.
I love it.
You got amazing advice.
I appreciate you guys.
Y'all, that's why you don't
take no for an answer, man.
We got the oil and gas
mogul coming down the street here.
He was on the run, but I'm always going to
do everything I can to get this game for you
guys.
It's not time to go.
It's a high school dropout.
Build a business doing more than $10 million a year.
Crazy interview out here in Beverly Hills.
Let's keep it rolling.
You guys come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, question for you.
How old were you when you made your first million?
I was 26.
What line of business were you in?
A little different than most.
You're not with the news, are you?
No.
Where are you from?
I have one of the biggest
business media channels in the world.
We grew a channel to 12 million followers.
Just asking people how they
made it for the younger generation.
So we're going to be
helping the younger people with this.
I was part of an organized crime group in
New York, and I made my first million dollars
that way.
Organized crime?
Organized crime.
Mafia.
You were in the mafia.
How did you get into the mafia?
My dad was the underboss of one of the
major families, the Colombo family, and my dad proposed
me for membership.
What's the most amount of money
that you made in a single day?
Well, let's go for a week.
I made $10 million in a week.
$10, $12 million.
We used to make between, we used to bring
into our operation $8 to $15 million a week.
How is that possible?
We were defrauding the government out
of tax on every gallon of gasoline.
I was selling a half a billion gallons of
gas a month, taking down 30, 40 cents a gallon.
We interview you for a minute real quick.
I ask you a couple
of quick questions with the chair.
As long as it's helping the kids, yeah.
Is that cool?
Yeah.
What's a lesson about business you learned
from doing business in the mafia that school
will never teach somebody?
Business is business.
It's whether you're doing it on the
street or you're doing it in the street.
If you're doing it in a legitimate
world, you got to follow a certain pattern.
I always went by the motto, do
what you do best, delegate the rest.
I got the right people around me.
I motivated them to do the
work that I knew I wouldn't do.
I was kind of the mastermind
or the leader and worked out.
Same way now.
You brought up delegating.
When you found those people, how did
you retain those A players, that top talent?
Because it's one of the
hardest things to do in business.
We know that talent is
ultimately the end game in business.
How do you keep great talent around you?
Treat them right.
Give me your expectations right up front.
Even though you're the boss and you're their leader.
I always said this.
There's a difference between a leader and being a boss.
A leader is only a leader
when somebody willingly wants to follow them.
And so if you set that tone with your
people and they believe in you and they're committed
to the business, that's when you
can have success and keep them.
Unless they're doing something wrong and you
know that they just want the right person.
Craziest deal you ever closed?
Oh, you don't want to know.
Tell me.
Craziest deal I ever closed
with the government, the US government.
Back when you were in the mafia?
Yeah.
How did that happen?
I would rival that with sitting down with John Gotti.
But the government was probably my
most successful negotiation was with the government.
Because if I didn't negotiate
properly, I wouldn't be standing here.
I'd be doing life in prison.
So how did you negotiate with the government?
I went in there with an advantage because
they wanted me really bad and I had beaten
them five times.
So I knew I had the edge on them.
They wanted to get a conviction on me.
And so if I was willing to give them
that, then they had to give me something in return.
Basically, I had a huge fine, huge restitution.
I had a helicopter, a jet plane.
I gave them all of that.
Gave them a bunch of money at the time.
But I got a very low prison sentence as
a result compared to what I could have gotten.
You went to prison.
I did.
I was in prison for six years.
What's the most interesting thing that you
learned about people while you were in prison?
I learned this in prison in a big way.
Anybody that's in prison that never got respect
on the street wanted all the respect in prison.
So I learned three things, three words that
will help you get through your prison time
pretty good.
Please, thank you, excuse me.
You want to cut somebody on the line?
Please, you don't mind if I get ahead?
You don't disrespect them by
just jumping in because that's disrespect.
They take it as a big thing.
Somebody hands you something, you say thank you.
You want something from somebody, you say please.
Those three words go a long way.
Do you believe in God?
I do.
How much?
I'm accountable to God in my life.
And I always say two things too.
You want success in life?
Get these two things right.
Number one, in this life we
are who we hang out with.
You have to surround yourself with
the right people, no question about it.
And number two, who you are accountable to in
life is going to direct the path that you
go on.
So now, when I was on the
street, I was accountable to my oath.
I took an oath.
I was accountable to my boss.
I was a criminal.
Now I'm accountable to my God first,
to my family, my wife, my children.
Don't want to get in trouble,
so I do the right thing.
Accountability is everything.
For somebody who's questioning their belief in God.
Trying to find that relationship.
What advice would you tell to them?
How did you find your relationship and belief in God?
You know, I was thrown in solitary confinement.
I actually spent three years, 29
months and seven days in solitary.
And it was during that time that
I believed that there was an afterlife.
There was an eternity.
And I wanted to study every religion.
Because I thought I was going to
spend the rest of my life in prison.
And that would have been it.
So I studied every faith.
And I came out of there
believing in Christianity with all my heart.
And you know, it's all about
for me a relationship with God.
It's not about rules, regulations.
How do you turn your life around?
It's about having faith.
Having a relationship and being accountable to God.
When that happens with you,
you're transformed from the inside out.
You know, I tell you this.
You can take the boy out of Brooklyn.
You can't always take Brooklyn out of a boy.
I still have the same thoughts I
had when I was on the street.
Sometimes things happen.
I want to react a certain way.
But now, accountability to God.
I don't want to get myself in trouble.
I don't want to put my family in that situation.
So I behave differently.
I react differently.
Even though the thought process can
be the same, I react differently.
Could you tell me about a time
where you got done wrong in business?
Well, that happened more than once.
Because remember.
You're in a relationship with people on the street.
So you put your little trust in somebody.
And you always, you never trust
anybody 100% no matter who it is.
But I trusted in people.
You know.
I'll give you an example.
This is a silly example.
But I'll give you an example.
There was a guy that was really in bad shape.
I gave him a job.
Right?
I gave him $3,500 a week.
Back then.
This was in the late 70s, early 80s.
To go to gas stations and collect my money.
Somebody handed him a paper bag.
They brought it to me.
That was it.
After about six months, he came
to me and asked for a raise.
And I said to him, do
you think you're worth $3,500 a week?
I'm doing you a favor.
What your problem is, you're counting the money
in the bag and looking at how much money
I'm making and think that you deserve that.
I said, so you're fired.
And he, you know, I wasn't going to fire him.
I was trying to teach him a lesson.
I said, no, you're fired.
Don't talk to me ever again.
You're gone.
And he came back because he really needed the money.
But I taught him a lesson.
Don't count my money.
Just do your job.
That's it.
Your last message to the younger generation.
Somebody, they don't come from money.
They don't come from a rich family.
They want to make it like you did.
What's your last message to the
younger generation watching this right now?
Give them one more golden nugget.
Let me tell you something.
Determination is everything.
Don't ever feel sorry for yourself.
Don't overthink somebody is going to
give you a handout or help you.
You got to work.
When I started, my dad went
away when I was a young kid.
I got in serious trouble.
I was on trial when I was 19 years old.
I had no money.
I had no money even to pay a lawyer.
But I was determined to make it.
So you got to do it on your own.
Don't expect anybody to help you.
You got to be determined
and don't let anybody dissuade you.
If you feel you have the ability to
do something, then it's your determination that's going
to make it happen.
Nothing else.
I love it.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Appreciate it.
Thank you so much for your time.
You got it.
Appreciate you.
Guys, one conversation with a billionaire changed
the way I think about money forever.
And that's why on May 28th, I'm doing something insane.
I'm bringing three billionaires right to you so
you can actually talk to them on a Zoom
call live and not just watch them.
And it's called Billionaire Day.
And it's our first ever virtual event where
we make it free to get access to billionaires.
Did you know that 99% of people will
never get mentored from a billionaire in their entire
life?
Well, on May 28th, I'm putting
you face to face with not one.
Not two, but three of them.
And it's 100% free.
This isn't a live stream.
This isn't a course.
This isn't a podcast.
It's three private live calls on Zoom
for one day with people who built generational
wealth, where you'll be able to
ask the billionaires your questions live.
And it's 100% free.
No pitch, no fluff, just pure value.
But there is one catch.
There will be no recordings.
There will be no replays.
You must be there live to get access.
So if you're seeing this before May 28th,
you can still get in and grab your spot.
That being said, once you miss
this, it will be gone forever.
I want you guys to understand that
there's 800 billionaires in the United States.
And on May 28th, I'm bringing three of
them on a live call right to you.
So if you've ever wanted to sign to
change your life, to build generational wealth and
start becoming financially free, this is it.
Literally, guys, this has never happened in history.
And I'm doing this to over deliver
for the School of Hard Knocks family.
So if you want a spot, all you have to
do is go down and click the link in the description
of this video.
And I'll see you on May 28th.
Along with the billionaires.
With that being said, let's go get this next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
Yes.
Question for you.
How old were you when you made your first million?
About 34.
How old are you now?
You're 52?
And what do you do for
a living out here in Beverly Hills?
I'm a plastic surgeon.
You're a plastic surgeon.
Do you own your own practice?
Yes.
How long have you been a business owner?
I've been in business here for about 13 years.
It's my 13th year.
And I go all over the world interviewing
the most successful business owners for the younger
generation.
Can I get one minute with
you for the channel real quick?
I'm waiting in my car.
Can you get a minute?
Just one second.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
$9 million.
So what was the worst financial
decision that you made throughout your career?
Marriage.
Actually?
You know, marrying the wrong person.
I love the Bible.
You know what I'm saying?
For you to do well in
life, it's part of God's principle.
It's partners to be there, you call it yoga.
Let's say a young entrepreneur is dating right now.
What's the biggest red flag that you would look
out for to tell you that that's not the
right person for you?
It's not the right person if
you guys don't share the same faith.
Period.
You have to share the same faith.
Because, you know, sharing the same
faith is not the right thing.
In a way, that means your values are in alignment.
You know, you have shared
values, shared beliefs, and shared disappointment.
So these are the things.
And if you can't share all these with one
person, you guys are not in sync, it won't
work out.
It won't work out.
And then when the home front is not
good, it takes away your attention to create.
Your creation, your creative methodology goes
down, and you don't want that.
Do you believe in God?
Oh, yes.
Without God, I would not be here.
How can a kid from
Ghana, from the slums of Ghana?
I grew up in a place called Ashtown.
How can a kid from Ashtown be on my
water stream making it to Beverly Hills to be one
of the best plastic surgeons in the world?
You're one of the best plastic
surgeons in the world, you said?
Yes, I do believe that, yes.
Have you ever met a billionaire before?
Of course.
I have a lot of billionaire friends.
And my goal is to be a
billionaire so I can do more work.
Actually, so how are you going to become a billionaire?
Give me the blueprint right now.
The blueprint?
Diversification.
I'm in the process of
launching a pharmaceutical plant in Ghana.
It's going to be the biggest plant in sub-Saharan Africa.
And when it's all said and
done, West Africa will have pharmaceutical emancipation.
That's the key to me becoming a billionaire.
That's incredible, man.
You think God wants people to be wealthy?
Yeah.
God talks about it in Genesis 1.26.
God wants people to be wealthy.
He says that, you know, go ahead.
Take dominion over the land.
God wants us all to prosper.
And even in Jeremiah 29.11, He says,
I have a plan for you to prosper.
So God wants us all to prosper, okay?
It's not about money because some people
are, you know, prosperous financially and some
people are prosperous in different avenues.
So God is the ultimate giver of wealth.
Oh, man.
That was amazing, my friend.
So it was.
We just interviewed a plastic surgeon out
here in Beverly Hills that made $9 million
in a single year.
And he said, I got goals to becoming a billionaire.
He said, I know a lot of billionaires.
I'm friends with them.
But I want to become a billionaire.
And what did he say he's doing?
He's building a pharmaceutical plant out in
Ghana in one of the wealthiest countries in
Africa.
Crazy good interview out here in Beverly Hills.
He just gave some amazing advice to you guys.
We got to keep this one rolling and go
get another one out here in Los Angeles, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, what did you do to become wealthy?
I actually roll burritos for a living.
You roll burritos?
I do.
What do you mean?
I'm the CEO of Chipotle Mexican Grill.
You're the CEO of Chipotle?
I am.
Do you think I could interview you real quick?
I go all over the world interviewing
the most successful people for the younger generation.
Can I get one minute with you first?
Sure.
Yeah, let's do it.
Is that okay?
Yeah, of course.
Did you come from a lot of money?
I did not.
So you didn't have rich parents?
I grew up in very humble beginnings.
How humble?
My first job was at
a McDonald's restaurant flipping burgers.
My high school career, I spent washing dishes.
We had to earn money.
So you went from dishwasher to the CEO
of one of the biggest companies in the world?
Pretty much.
How in the world does that happen?
Come on.
Look back at your career.
Whether you recognize it or not,
you're building a reputation within your industry.
But I would tell you, you're always interviewing.
And whether you think others are watching or
not, believe me, they are, you will be
judged on your ability to drive performance.
And I'll tell you, you're always interviewing.
And I'll tell you, you
earn credibility by delivering results.
I'll stop.
I always say that credibility kills all bad attitudes.
It sure does.
Everyone celebrates the winners.
You know how you network with successful people?
Become successful.
There you go.
I love it.
What is Chipotle going to do in revenue this year?
We'll push close to $13 billion this
year in annual sales, which is really incredible
for our organization.
We still feel like we can double
that over the next five to 10 years.
How is that possible?
Just through growth and scale, both
in organic restaurant growth, individual restaurant growth
as it relates to comp sales
performance, but also in new restaurant growth.
This year, we'll build between 315 to 340.
We're opening at Chipotle almost
every 24 hours here in 2025.
And we believe we can get to 7,000
restaurants in North America and then probably double
that again outside the United States.
How many locations does Chipotle have right now?
Just over 3,800.
But you guys, there's no franchising with Chipotle.
No franchising.
Why not?
I think it's important for us
to protect the integrity of the brand.
And I have been largely unwilling at this
point to allow someone else to run the brand
because I don't know that anyone can
do it better than we can internally.
And so I think brands get into franchising when
they get to a scale that they feel like
they can't manage or they need investment.
And so they look for other partners.
At Chipotle, we have an extraordinary balance sheet.
We call it a fortress balance sheet.
We have just over $2 billion in cash
or cash equivalents on the balance sheet with zero
debt today.
And we generate enough cash to continue to
put cash in our reserves, do share buybacks
quarterly, as well as support our own growth.
What's the best advice you ever received from a mentor?
That business school won't teach somebody.
So there's a difference
between responsibility and accountability.
If you and I are both
responsible for a task, who's accountable?
No one.
We talk about this idea
in operations around who's accountable.
Who's the one person that has
to ensure that this job gets done?
We may share responsibility, but one
of us has to be accountable.
You know they don't teach that in school, right?
I know.
Do you have another business analogy like
that that could help some people out?
There's an old adage in this industry,
you can't save your way to prosperity.
And I would lean into this idea of
abundance versus scarcity, meaning I continue to invest
in the consumer experience, continue to invest
in the team member experience, and that will
always pay outsized dividends for you and your firm.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate you.
Good spending time with you guys.
Thanks, man.
Scott.
Scott, great to meet you.
Yeah.
Good to meet you, bro.
You guys, Beverly Hills was incredible, but I
need you guys to like and subscribe for
amazing content we've got coming every single
week because I'm traveling the world every
week to go find and interview the
wealthiest and the most successful business owners for
you.
And if you watching this right now
want direct access to the millionaires and billionaires
that I interview, I give it to you
guys every single week inside of my private entrepreneur
community that I built this last year that
has now become the number one community for
business owners in the entire world.
Because every single week you have the ability
to get access to the people that I interview.
It's so cool.
I get to interview on live calls where
you can ask your questions directly to them and
get personalized one on one
mentorship and advice every week.
So if you want to join the community,
the school of mentors, the number one community
for business owners in the world, go down
to the link in the description of this video.
I can't wait to see you on the inside.
With that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.